arnebrachhold.de 2010-06-26

# Privacy Policy

I promise not to disclose your private information to any third party except if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of the users of this website or the public. I take all reasonable care in handling your personal information to ensure its security both offline and online.

#### Types of Information I Collect

You are free to browse this website without submitting any personal information at all. Your IP address (your current Internet address) is stored in the server logs at the time of your visit, as it is on all web sites. I do not collect any personal information (such as a name, address or e-mail address) when you visit the site unless you register to the site or provied the information when leaving a comment.

#### Postings Comments on Articles

It is important remember that when you provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number) in a online posting that that information is visible to anyone, and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason, I discourage you from posting any personal information on this or any website in comments or otherwise.

#### Cookies

The WordPress Blog Software use browser cookies to keep track of which messages you have read, and other information about your session. Cookies are small pieces of text that are stored on your hard drive between visits. For example, I use a cookie to store your name and URL when you post comments so you don’t have to re-enter them each time you visit. These cookies do not collect, store or maintain any private, personally identifiable information. You do not have to accept these cookies to visit or use the site (although turning cookies off will impair the site’s functionality), and you can choose to refuse the cookies, delete the cookies from your hard drive or turn off cookies at any time by updating your user profile preferences.
